const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "4.8",
    title: "Modals - can, should, must, have to",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "Umiem mówić w pięciu językach.",
    back: "I can speak five languages.",
  },
  {
    front: "Powinieneś pracować jako przewodnik turystyczny.",
    back: "You should work as a tour guide.",
  },
  {
    front: "Muszę przynieść ciasto na przyjęcie.",
    back: "I have to bring a cake to the party."
  },
  {
    front: "Czy możesz kupić ciasto?",
    back: "Can you buy the cake?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy musisz zrobić ciasto własnoręcznie?",
    back: "Do you have to make the cake yourself?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co powinienem zrobić?/ Co powinnam zrobić?",
    back: "What should I do?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie możemy zrobić sobie przerwy.",
    back: "We can't take a break.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie powinieneś tak ciężko pracować.",
    back: "You shouldn't work so hard.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie wolno cie zabierać tych dokumentów do domu.",
    back: "You mustn't take these documents home.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie musisz zawsze mówić 'tak'.",
    back: "You don't have to always say 'yes'.",
  },
  {
    front: "Ona potrafi bardzo dobrze prowadzić auto.",
    back: "She can drive very well.",
  },
  {
    front: "Powinna kupić lepszy samochód.",
    back: "She should buy a better car.",
  },
  {
    front: "Ona musi negocjować cenę.",
    back: "She has to negotiate the price.",
  },
  {
    front: "Co możesz zaoferować?",
    back: "What can you offer?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie powinnam pojechać?",
    back: "Where should I go?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy on musi nosić okulary?",
    back: "Does he have to wear glasses?",
  },
  {
    front: "On nie widzi bez okularów.",
    back: "He can't see without glasses.",
  },
  {
    front: "On nie powinien wychodzić z domu bez okularów.",
    back: "He shouldn't leave the house without glasses.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie wolno mu prowadzić bez okularów.",
    back: "He mustn't drive without glasses.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie musi kupować nowych okularów. Stare są w porządku.",
    back: "He doesn't have to get new glasses. The old ones are OK.",
  },
  {
    front: "Możesz to zrobić!",
    back: "You can do it!",
  },
  {
    front: "Powinieneś spróbować!",
    back: "You should try!",
  },
  {
    front: "Musisz mi uwierzyć.",
    back: "You have to believe me.",
  },
  {
    front: "Możesz mi pomóc?",
    back: "Can you give me a hand?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy mógłbyś mi pomóc?",
    back: "Could you give me a hand?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy musimy jutro wstać wcześnie?",
    back: "Do we have to get up early tomorrow?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie możemy spóźnić się na samolot.",
    back: "We can't be late for the flight.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie powinieneś palić.",
    back: "You shouldn't smoke.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie wolno tu parkować.",
    back: "You mustn't park here.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie musisz przepraszać.",
    back: "You don't have to apologise.",
  },
];
export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
